<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>XR on UC Berkeley CTO Blog</title><link>/tags/xr/</link><description>Recent content in XR on UC Berkeley CTO Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2025 UC Regents; all rights reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/xr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UC Berkeley Podcast Studio- Engaging &amp; Amplifying Student Voices</title><link>/blog/2022-04-01-uc-berkeley-podcast-studio-engaging-amplifying-student-voices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022-04-01-uc-berkeley-podcast-studio-engaging-amplifying-student-voices/</guid><description>Through the Berkeley Changemakers Innovation Grant, Dr. Pablo Gonzalez and his team have created a fully functioning podcast studio for students, faculty, and staff to utilize. The purpose of this studio is to give the UC Berkeley community a platform to amplify their voices.</description></item><item><title>Lucid Learning - 2020 Berkeley Changemaker Technology Innovation Grant Awardee [ARCHIVE]</title><link>/blog/2020-12-08-lucid-learning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/blog/2020-12-08-lucid-learning/</guid><description>Lucid Learning is a tool to help students practice collaboration early in their careers.</description></item><item><title>RTL AR/VR - 2020 Berkeley Changemaker Technology Innovation Grant Awardee [ARCHIVE]</title><link>/blog/2020-12-08-rtl-ar-vr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/blog/2020-12-08-rtl-ar-vr/</guid><description>RTL will partner with the CTO and our AR/VR 2020 Berkeley Changemaker Technology Innovation Grant awardees to develop a community of practice for AR/VR supporting instruction and research.</description></item><item><title>VRTutor - 2020 Berkeley Changemaker Technology Innovation Grant Awardee [ARCHIVE]</title><link>/blog/2020-12-08-vrtutor-changemaker-awardee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/blog/2020-12-08-vrtutor-changemaker-awardee/</guid><description>This project, submitted by professor Luisa Caldas and Architecture, Building Science and Technology researcher Elnaz Tafrihi Bailey will fund the development of a Virtual, Augmented and Mixed Reality (VR/AR/MR) tool developed by the College of Environmental Design.</description></item></channel></rss>